Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
A dungeon surfaced near the border between the Clover and Diamond Kingdoms.
Asta, Noelle, and Luck of the Black Bulls were dispatched to explore it
and prevent the treasures concealed within from falling into enemy hands.
Whoa, this is like the most awesome place ever!
Hey, take a look at this, Asta! Right there!
I don't see anything.
No, sir!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
The dungeon was thick with mana and teeming with traps.
Wow, the looks on your faces!
That was fun, huh?
I could play in this place all day!
This guy is totally going to get us killed!
Now, let's see what we've got.
I'm just about at my limit.
I knew it!
We're not alone in here.
And the strongest of them all is.
Sorry guys, but something important has come up!
I gotta get going!
Huh?
You two just go ahead and get through the dungeon on your own and I'll see you soon, okay?
It's okay, we've got nothing to worry about.
Whatever traps are in this place, my sword will slice right through them. Easy.
We're alone now. It's just the two of us.
What's up? Is something wrong?
No, of course not!
Insect!
Well, hurry!
Oh no! It's a trap!
Give me a sec!
Asta and Noelle found themselves in grave danger, but just then.
Not good.
Oh crap!
Such powerful magic, and precision too.
But whose spell was that?
And with that, my debt is paid.
Asta.
Hey, you know.
Are you sure?
What's going through the hell?
The biggest gamble?
Are you in love with my yet?
It's too strange to be through m熟?
Are you sure?
Do you want to.
Yeah, you, you keep wherever I go.
I don't know.
You're losing through dragon out.
You're losing through that amine.
Yes, you're losing through dragon out!
What were you losing?
There was a spot on you.
Don't be inャ passwords.
dit you stay off ii left.
Oh
Captain Vongence
Yes, Alecdora, what is it?
Sir, I have some concerns regarding the exploration of the newly discovered dungeon
Forgive me, but why send an untried commoner on such a crucial mission?
Do I have your trust as your leader and captain?
Yes, of course
I would follow you anywhere, do anything you asked
Even should it mean my death
I trust you
That's good
I trust the untried commoner, as you called him
And I would ask you to do the same
After all, he is a full-fledged member of the Golden Dawn
And for the sake of the squad
I am certain he will only continue to grow stronger
Sir
Yes, our new member must grow stronger
He must
So this is Yuno
And that's...
Hmm
Yuno
Sir, why did you go out of your way to save these people?
We've been charged with exploring this dungeon and securing its valuable contents
Our primary objective is to reach the treasure hall at its heart with all possible haste
We have no time to involve ourselves with such rabble as these
Jeez, who the hell is Four Eyes the Rude here?
My superior
Excuse me?
And you think that I'm rude?
Don't say that again, brat!
I am a noble and you will treat me with respect!
So much for not involving ourselves
Fancy running into you here, Noelle
We haven't seen each other since last year's Royal Banquet, isn't that right?
You know each other?
Yes, just a bit
Actually, I'm Noelle's cousin
Huh?
Well, this is quite a surprise
It just had to be her
From what I've heard, the Black Bulls can be a rather unrefined squad at times
Are you doing alright with them?
I think that's what I should be asking you, Mimosa
Can you actually keep up with the elite members of the Golden Dawn, Dimbulb that you are?
Sure!
Everyone is just so incredibly kind
I can wield my magic with no qualms at all, knowing I have their support
Oh!
How thoughtless of me when you've always had to struggle so much with learning to control your own magic
Has that gotten any better?
Clearly, the girl still doesn't have a filter
Just fantastic
Yes, it's coming along fine, thank you
Great!
It's so wonderful that we're both finding our footing as magic knights
The Wizard King even gave us a star for our last mission
Hmm
What a coincidence!
We got a star for our last mission, too!
You're a liar
Brand new members of the Slipshot Black Bulls?
It's inconceivable that you could earn a star so easily
Well, we did so there!
And our total is up to negative 30 now!
Huh!
Not a chance!
Why you're being sent on this mission is absurd enough!
Guess the Wizard King didn't think so, cause he's the one who sent me!
Yet another bald-faced lie!
It is not a lie!
Huh!
Yeah, we're definitely involved
Now that I think of it, I was told that there were going to be three of you
So where is your third member?
Uh
What?
Did they run away and leave you here to explore the dungeon on your own?
Was that it?
Or perhaps they fell victim to a trap spell?
Huh!
He didn't run away, and he didn't get caught in some trap
So where is he then?
Almost there
He took off into the dungeon because he's basically nuts?
Thanks luck
Cocker
Whatever the case, he's a coward who left his newest colleagues behind
A typical Black Bull
How disgusting!
Your whole squad brings shame to the Magic Knights
Okay, now you've really done it, pal
The Black Bulls are going to conquer this dungeon so fast you won't even know what hit you!
Just you watch!
Golden Dumb!
Uh, Golden Tim!
No, uh, squad with the weird-haired boss!
I've heard enough!
First you insult our intelligence, and then our captain!
How dare you!
Mocking our leader, the incomparable Captain Vongeance!
You will pay!
Besides, you're the one whose captain walks around in a rally old top
Blotting his over-inflated muscles and smoking like a chimney!
What are you, crazy?!
Or maybe you're just jealous, cause Yami's manlier than you!
I am a senior Magic Knight and a noble!
Show some respect, you filth!
Oh!
Begging your pardon, sir!
I'm so sorry!
Damn you!
The involved doesn't even begin to cover it
All right, enough of this idiocy
I'll show you the difference between the top Magic Knight squad in the kingdom
And the one that doesn't deserve the name
Mimosa!
Sure
All right, play it creation magic
Magic flower guidepost!
Let's see...
Yes, yes...
Okay
I've got the dungeon's layout
I should be able to find the treasure hall
Good
You know?
Yes, sir
They all make it look so easy
Do your best, poor as it is
Good work, you know
Yeah
Let's go!
You coming?
Hey!
Wait, no!
No!
We'll fight to see who will reach the treasure hall first
Whatever it takes
I'm can hear the treasure
Like this
Yeah
You can hear the treasure camera
I promise the treasure
Oh!
And those who will be recovering
I know
I'll just raise your breath
So...
Thanks to this
You can see
I'll just see youreti
It's time you can see
Great, now what do we do?
It's not as if either of us are equipped to use exploration magic, you know.
We just check out every path until we find the right one!
Let's do this!
What are you, insane?
Oh yeah, that's right, you are!
This ingenious idea of yours isn't going to get us anywhere but lost.
Nero?
Next we take a right.
Okay.
That brat's name was Oster, that little fool.
Does he honestly think he can get the better of us?
He does seem a most unusual boy.
I sense not a bit of magic power in him.
No, neither did I.
What was that Black Bull captain thinking?
How could someone like that be of any use to a magic night squad?
Klaus, sir.
Oster's strong.
I would suggest not underestimating him.
As far as I'm concerned, it will be a miracle if they make it out of here alive.
All we need to concentrate on is capturing this dungeon swiftly for the good of our kingdom.
Reporting, Wizard King, sir.
Teams have been dispatched by the Golden Dawn and the Black Bulls.
They have begun their exploration of the dungeon.
Also, we have confirmed that the Diamond Kingdom's mage troops have entered as well.
What in the Diamond Kingdom?
They'd better not sit their hands on the dungeon's treasure.
They've been particularly focused on expanding their territory.
They're always the aggressor.
If we let their people take the ancient magic from the dungeon, who knows what kind of trouble they'll cause.
These Diamond Mage troops, who's their leader?
Sir, the enemy troops appear to be commanded by Lotus of the Abyss.
We met on the battlefield once upon a time.
He was certainly tough.
Crafty.
Uses the most interesting magic, too.
Sir, this is no time to be so nonchalant.
A graver tone, please.
All will be well, don't worry.
I believe Yami also sent along someone interesting.
Still.
Lotus may be powerful, Marks.
But our young recruits?
They are, too.
You're all so weak.
But you're much stronger than them, right?
Well, I don't know about all that.
Don't like to raise expectations.
It only leads to disappointment.
So much raw, young power.
I'm intimidated, to be honest.
You took out my underlings with so little effort.
Truly impressive.
Like you said, they were underlings.
They can afford to be weak so long as their leader is powerful.
I see that you fight by surrounding yourself with lightning magic.
How very resourceful of you.
Your attacks must pack quite a punch.
You're fast, as well.
And all of that is fed by your youthful vigor.
My.
You got this old man scared, all right.
And what about you, then?
What magic do you fight with?
Hmm.
Goodness.
You are an eager one, aren't you?
I'm assuming you Clover folks came in search of the dungeon's treasure hall, too.
Yeah.
Now let's fight!
Oh, I don't know.
I mean, it's not like we really need to fight.
We could just have a nice, friendly foot race.
No violence or bloodshed necessary.
What do you think?
It sounds like a good idea to me.
Come on, let's go.
Get away!
Fast indeed.
Touch.
Smoke?
Oh, I'm terribly frightened.
Hmm.
I can understand why your people would be so angry with mine.
Obviously, no one likes having their country invaded.
I don't blame you.
Truly.
And we of the Diamond Kingdom apologize for the inconvenience.
It's just, we found ourselves running low on resources, you know?
What choice do we have if we want to live?
Living can be so very hard.
See, I have three daughters of my own I need to provide for.
Oh, yeah?
Whatever, old man.
I'm just happy to finally be fighting somebody powerful.
You're a real piece of work.
You know that, right?
You may reduce me to tears.
What's with this place?
The gravity's gone haywire.
Hey, bird brain, are you sure this is the right way?
Come on!
Nero!
Wake up!
Look at that!
It's treasure!
It definitely is not!
Don't go after it!
Only a complete idiot wouldn't see that it's a trap.
All right!
Got you now.
Stop!
Don't open it!
My sweet treasure chest!
What's inside of you?
Will you let it go?
What are you going to do if it's a trap?
And open!
Why didn't you just make me look at, you jerk?
It's not like I knew what was...
You're quite a hot-blooded youth.
It's no fun if you just dodge my attacks.
Fight back!
Well?
Oh, come on!
Phew.
Ah, yes.
I remember that, Rogue.
You're a black bull, aren't you?
I actually had the dubious honor of fighting your captain once.
He was a spitfire like you.
Wow!
You really know Captain Yami?
I'm not likely to forget him either.
Not after he left me such a splendid memento.
Wet my pants and ran as fast as I could.
Now, that was truly a scary fellow.
He had a rather unique fighting style.
He was the only person younger than me who I couldn't defeat.
You're totally worth fighting!
Oh?
You don't look well, something wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
Too slow.
Down you go now.
Nice and easy.
Down into the abyss.
What's going on?
A spell?
Oh, but...
I don't remember being hit with anything.
You see, I have something to confess.
The air in here is full of my magic power.
An extremely thin smoke, too thin for the eye to see.
Oh, and in case you're interested, it's called weakening smoke magic.
Garden of plundering smoke.
My body...
It's not moving right...
Magic that reduces physical ability.
But when did he...
Visible attacks can only do so much.
They're easy enough for an opponent to dodge.
I opted for a more subtle approach.
So I used every last drop of my magic power and cast it stealthily.
Fighting off my underlings provided a more than adequate distraction.
Their defeat was regrettable, but it wasn't in vain.
Their sacrifice gave me the opportunity to work my magic.
You know, it truly is vital.
Teamwork.
We're almost there now.
It should be just through this hallway.
Isn't that simply marvelous?
Some dungeon that was.
Not much to it at all.
So what's your plan for getting past this?
It doesn't appear as if the Black Bulls have managed to find it yet.
Of course they haven't.
Despite their bluster, they never stood a chance of beating us here.
You're probably right.
Mimosa!
It pierced through her cloak of magical defense.
Such a keen mana sense, but she never saw it coming.
She's still alive.
This is no trap magic.
So, what is it?
Who goes there?
You're in my way.
Now move.
See what you really need.
Our friends, you know you can count on.
Well, sorry about this, but I've got things to do.
You know how it is.
Win.
Keep on winning.
Luck.
Hold on.
It's been too long.
Since things have gotten this interesting.
Oh, yeah.
Let's do this.
Time to fight.
So much potential.
I'm almost sorry to extinguish it.
Let's do this.
I can find a place to go.
消えそうな光でも闇を照らす力が
繋がって時の流れを変える
I'm living in me
色褪せない場所に
Brain for yourself
終わらない夢を掴むため
進むべき道があるなら
Do you wanna drive?
このままどこまででも
僕の命が終わるまで
どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can drive down.
たとえ明日が見えなくても
声にならない
想いを抱いて
叫び続ける
ご視聴ありがとうございました
Clover Cliffs
A lotus
that won't bloom
is just another water lily
See
I have three daughters
of my own
I need to provide for
When I'm all grown up
I'm gonna marry daddy
My girls dote on me
but of course
there's no telling
how long that will last
Oh yes
I can just hear it now
Go away
We can take care
of our own laundry
Teenagers are truly scary
What a sad man
Sounds like he could
really use a good fight
to cheer him up
Now forget about it
It's not over yet
Things are finally
getting good
Let's play some more
Let's see who dies first
Okay old man
Black Clover page 16
Friends
My magic is never giving up